[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "To what continent is the unique Maned Wolf endemic?", "correct_answer": "South America", "incorrect_answers": ["Asia", "Africa", "Europe"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "How are Neil and Max related in the film Dirty Dancing?", "correct_answer": "Neil is Maxs grandson.", "incorrect_answers": ["Max is Neils father.", "Neil is Maxs uncle.", "Max is Neils uncle."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "He was the first NHL player to buy his former team.", "correct_answer": "Mario Lemieux", "incorrect_answers": ["Wayne Gretsky", "Gordie Howe", "Patrick Roy"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Nicotine can be found in tomatoes, potatoes, green peppers, coca plants and tobacco.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Is it true that according to the Smallville series, Black Kryptonite splits Clark into two separate beings?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This Microsoft operating system, formerly codenamed Blackcomb and Vienna, is intended to succeed Windows Vista.", "correct_answer": "7", "incorrect_answers": ["Mojave", "Vista", "Mac OS X Leopard"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "German chemist Martin Klaproth discovered uranium in what year?", "correct_answer": "1789", "incorrect_answers": ["1891", "1938", "678"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the popular Norwegian delicacy called Smalahove made from?", "correct_answer": "Lamb head", "incorrect_answers": ["Pork intestines", "Fish liver", "Chicken popes nose"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Blazing Saddles, Bart was going to be hanged for committing what crime?", "correct_answer": "Hitting Taggart over the head with a shovel", "incorrect_answers": ["Refusing to work", "Walking off the job", "Hitting Lyle over the head with a shovel"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "According to Feng Shui the toilet should be this.", "correct_answer": "Hidden.", "incorrect_answers": ["It does not matter where the toiler is.", "Attached to the bedroom.", "Always open."]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the United States Navy, what is the next rank above Ensign?", "correct_answer": "Lieutenant (junior grade)", "incorrect_answers": ["2nd Lieutenant", "Chief Petty Officer", "Captain"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following is the title of one of Aesops most famous fables?", "correct_answer": "The Fox and the Grapes", "incorrect_answers": ["The Cat and the Rat", "The Elephant and the Flea", "The Crow and the Scarecrow"]}]